

Abdul Aziz

Hello, Abdul Aziz is my name. I am a very motivated and hardworking person. I spent my time learning new things to further my expertise, such as reading books and attending Rubicamp coding bootcamp courses. My present job is as a freelancer working on a project to build applications for various businesses/ companies.

Semarang City, Central Java, Indonesia







Skills



Projects



Mobile Application

Pilgrimage Monitoring for the Abadan Land Arrangement Company.



Website Application

Point of Sales System Website Application for Lurik Rachmad Company.

Work Experience



Full-Stack Developer Freelancer

October 2022 - Present

I have completed several member data management application projects for OKK Central Java Province, pilgrimage monitoring applications for the Abadan Land Arrangement, and am currently working on a project to build a point of sale application for Lurik Rachmad and a point of sale application for the Bina Niaga savings and loan cooperative.



Internship in the division of Information Technology (IT). PT. Promanufacture Indonesia - Formulatrix

September 2021 - December 2021

Gain experience and understanding in computer hardware management, as well as installation and maintenance of security cameras or CCTV.

Education



July - October 2022

Rubicamp Coding Bootcamp Full-Stack Developer



2018 - 2022

SMK Negeri 7 (STM Pembangunan) Semarang

Power Electronics and Communication